[
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 1,
      "veggie_question": "Name a fruit that starts with 'A'. It is white on the inside and can be red, yellow, or green on the outside.",
      "veggie_answer": "Apple",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 2,
      "veggie_question": "Name a spiny, green vegetable that starts with 'A'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Artichoke",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 3,
      "veggie_question": "Name a long, thin fruit that starts with 'B'. It is yellow on the outside and white on the inside.",
      "veggie_answer": "Banana",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 4,
      "veggie_question": "Name a long, thin, orange vegetable that grows underground. It starts with a 'C'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Carrot",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 5,
      "veggie_question": "Name a crisp, green vegetable that has long stalks. It starts with 'C'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Celery",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 6,
      "veggie_question": "Name a yellow vegetable that grows on a cob and starts with 'C'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Corn",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 7,
      "veggie_question": "Name a vegetable that is green on the outside and white on the inside. It starts with 'C'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Cucumber",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 8,
      "veggie_question": "Name a purple vegetable that starts with 'E'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Eggplant",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 9,
      "veggie_question": "Name a big fruit that starts with 'G'. It can be yellow or pink and sometimes squirts you when you eat it.",
      "veggie_answer": "Grapefruit",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 10,
      "veggie_question": "Name a sweet fruit that grows in bunches on vines. It starts with 'G'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Grapes",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 11,
      "veggie_question": "You can cook fruit with sugar to make a sweet spread that tastes good on bread. What is this spread called? It starts with 'J'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Jam",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 12,
      "veggie_question": "Name a sour, yellow fruit that starts with 'L'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Lemon",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 13,
      "veggie_question": "Name a green, leafy vegetable that tastes good in salads. It starts with an 'L'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Lettuce",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 14,
      "veggie_question": "Name a sour, green fruit that starts with 'L'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Lime",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 15,
      "veggie_question": "Name a type of big fruit that has a rind. It starts with 'M'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Melon",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 16,
      "veggie_question": "Name an oily, green fruit that starts with 'O'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Olive",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 17,
      "veggie_question": "Name a sharp-tasting vegetable that starts with 'O'. It grows underground.",
      "veggie_answer": "Onion",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 18,
      "veggie_question": "Name a sweet fruit that start with the letter 'P' and grows on trees. ",
      "veggie_answer": "Peach",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 19,
      "veggie_question": "Name a tiny, round green vegetable that grows in pods. It starts with 'P'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Peas",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 20,
      "veggie_question": "Name a vegetable that is brown on the outside and white on the inside. It grows underground and starts with the letter 'P'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Potato",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 21,
      "veggie_question": "Name an orange vegetable that can be made into pie. It starts with 'P'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Pumpkin",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 22,
      "veggie_question": "What do you get when you dry a plum? It starts with 'P'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Prune",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 23,
      "veggie_question": "What do you get when you dry a grape? It starts with 'R'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Raisin",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 24,
      "veggie_question": "Name a sweet, red fruit that starts with 'S'.",
      "veggie_answer": "Strawberry",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 25,
      "veggie_question": "Name a soft, red fruit that starts with 'T'. It is not sweet.",
      "veggie_answer": "Tomato",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
      },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 26,
      "veggie_question": "Name a sweet fruit that starts with 'W'. It is green on the outside and pink on the inside.",
      "veggie_answer": "Watermelon",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
      },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 27,
      "veggie_question": "Name a sweet, orange vegetable that starts with 'Y'. It grows underground and can be made into pie.",
      "veggie_answer": "Yam",
      "answers": [
        "correct",
        "incorrect"
      ]
    }
  ]